# AHMAD DANY FATHIN NAWWAF

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

# PERSONAL PROFILE

I 'am a graduate of the Madiun State Polytechnic majoring in Computer Control Engineering at 2020 with GPA of 3.68 and studied at Wearnes Education Centre D1 of Informatics Engineering, Android, and Game Developer. I have knowledge, skill and experience in Wearnes for 1 years by building website, console application, and Mobile App. I 'am interested in new Technology such as Developer.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Part Time**

RSI SITI AISYAH MADIUN | Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

- Record incoming and claim BPJS
- Scanning and record data to upload in database
- Recap data from lab and radiology

## On The Job Training as Technician

Sharp Direct Service Station | Jul 2020 - Sept 2020

- · Repair Fridge, Television, and Washing Machine
- Welding Compressor Connection
- Freon Filling

# **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

# Polytechnic Madiun - Madiun, Indonesia

**Computer Control Engineering** 

Diploma 3 in A.Md. GPA - 3.68 | Aug 2017 - Sept 2020

- Learning C++ Programming Language
- Learning building and programming Robotics control
- Learning PLC controllers using Simens and Omron Media

#### Wearnes Education Centre - Madiun, Indonesia

Informatics, Android, and Game Developer Engineering
Diploma 1 | Aug 2022 - Sept 2023

- Learning C# Console
- Learning Web Developer and database
- Learning Android and Game Develop
- Learning Networking





Jalak Street No 11 Madiun city 63128



Madiun - March 20, 1999

# **CONTACT ME AT**



+62 89 5352 88 222 8

M

danyahmadadfn@gmail.com

github.com/AhmadDFN

<u>(0)</u>

instagram.com/ahmad\_dfn/

in

linkedin.com/in/ahmaddfn/

## SKILLS

#### Frontend:

Html, CSS.

#### Backend:

PHP, Laravel.

## **Programming Language:**

C++, C#, PHP, JavaScript.

#### **Robotics:**

Ardiuno IDE

#### **Mobile App:**

MIT App Inventor, Ionic

# Networking

Winbox, Packet Tracer